Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Secretary's office, Yale University, records
1838-2007
RU 52
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
283.42
389 boxes, 2 folios
660.83
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, degree records, reports, logs, and minutes documenting lectures; the Yale Corporation; honors, awards and prizes; the University Council; events and commemorations; commencement; community relations; and other matters handled by the secretary's office, primarily during and after the tenure of Henry Chauncey, Jr. Also included are minutes of the Council of Masters, Corporation index records, photographs of Yale regalia, and a DVD video montage celebrating Richard C. Levin's first ten years as president of Yale and records from the Fair Labor Association (FLA) and Workers Rights Consortium (WRC), reports on sweatshops, licensing deposits and royalty reports.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
Chauncey, Henry, Jr., 1935-
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Secretary, 1966-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Biographical / Historical
The secretary is an administrative officer elected by the Yale Corporation on nomination of the president. The secretary prepares and keeps the records of the Corporation and in addition to being responsible for the safekeeping of the seal and other official University insignia, also supervises the election of alumni fellows to the Corporation, helps the president prepare all diplomas and certificates of award, and is responsible for the management of all official University functions and publications. The secretary works with a staff of associates which oversees such non-academic areas as the University Archives, the University Council, public information, university security, and community relations.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Related Materials
Records of the secretary's office, Yale University (RU 49), Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, degree records, reports, logs, and minutes documenting lectures; the Yale Corporation; honors, awards and prizes; the University Council; events and commemorations; commencement; community relations; and other matters handled by the secretary's office, primarily during and after the tenure of Henry Chauncey, Jr. Also included are minutes of the Council of Masters, Corporation index records, photographs of Yale regalia, and a DVD video montage celebrating Richard C. Levin's first ten years as president of Yale and records from the Fair Labor Association (FLA) and Workers Rights Consortium (WRC), reports on sweatshops, licensing deposits and royalty reports.
Commencement ceremonies; Degrees, Academic; Lectures and lecturing; Speeches, addresses, etc.; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Awards; Yale University -- Degrees; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale Corporation; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Topical files documenting Yale regalia, 1876-1982; Accession 19ND-A-507
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Coats of arms: the university and the colleges, 1917-1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Logo, Circa 1876 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Regalia: Yale mace, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Seal, 1902, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Symbols: "The Yale" (mythological animal), 1982, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- University flow charts, circa 1966; Accession 1966-A-002
  - University flow charts, circa 1966 (Box AF2)
- Records of Henry Chauncey, Jr., concerning institutional research and the bicentennial, 1963-1977; Accession 1977-A-008
  - General Files
    - A - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academic Regalia, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Accreditation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Data Systems, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Afro-American House, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Afro-American Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alterations, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Associations and Clubs, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Board, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Board Fall Convocation, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Board - Los Angeles Regional Meeting, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Board National Meeting, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Complaints, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Commission, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Day, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Fellow, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Fund Orientation Program, 1970 November 23 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Fund Convocation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Fund Convocation, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Fund Convocation Panel Speech, 1970 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Magazine, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Organizations: Charts, 19767-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Placement Service, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Records, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - American Alumni Council, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - American Red Cross Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Andover Headmastership, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Application Forms (Clubs) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Archives, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Art and Architecture, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Art Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Art Gallery Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Art Gallery Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Art Gallery, Friends of American Arts, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Arts Proposal, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Association of Colleges in New England, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Communications Volunteers, background on (confidential), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Admissions, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Communications Group, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 43 - 44)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Communications Group, Including Charter, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Communications Group, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Founding Board of Governors, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Convocation, 1952-1972 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, General, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Seminar, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, Study Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - B - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Babbidge, Homer D., Jr., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Baccalaureate, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Bach Society, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Banner, Yale, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Barrington, Barrfe Fez, Laboratories for Metaphoric Environments, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Black Student Alliance, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Bowl, Yale, use of, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Brownell's Mid-Career Visiting Committee, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Buildings, Naming of Yale, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Bulletin Series Information, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - C - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Calendar, Undergraduate, Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Calendars (Weekly), other institutions, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Calendar, Undergraduate, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Calendar, Undergraduate, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Calendar, Undergraduate Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Campus Police (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Capital Requirements and Budgets Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Career Advisory, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Charter Flight, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Charities Drive, 11971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Class of 1972, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Class of 1975, Addresses, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Clerical Bureau, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Coeducation, University Committee on, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Coeducation, Yale College: An Analysis of the impact of Coeducation at Yale college", 1972 January (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Coeducation Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Residential Colleges, 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Residential College Deanships, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Residential College Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Residential College Masterships, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - College Seminars, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Commencement 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Honorary Degree Luncheon, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Commencement 1972 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Commencement and Reunions, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Communications Office, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Community Health Care Center, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Computer Center, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Conferences, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Conferences, 1970-1975- (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Connecticut Concilium College Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Connecticut Concilium Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Council of Masters, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Council, Yale College (Student), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Credit Cards (University), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Crisis Procedures, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Dahl Commission, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - D - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Davenport College, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Davenport College Mastership, 1971, undated (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Deans - Junior Group Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Deaths, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Degrees, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Degrees Conferred by Yale, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - DeVane Lectures, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - DeVane Medal, 1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - DeVane Professorship, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Development Board, 1971, undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Development Board Convocation, 1972 November 17-18 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Development Board Convocation Report, 1971 November 18-20 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Development Board Convocation, 1970 November 13 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Development Office, 1967-1973 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Dining Halls, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Diplomas, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Directories, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Discipline, Undergraduate, 1970, undated (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Division of Overseas Ministries Assembly, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Divinity School, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Dozier Committee, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Drama School, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Draft, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Timothy Dwight College, Seminar on Admissions, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - E - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Educational Policy Committee, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Educational Research, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Educational Corporation, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Educational American Leaders, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Eli International, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Yale Engineering Association, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Engineering and Applied Science, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - English Language Programs, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Enormous room, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Enrollment Numbers in University, 1964-1973 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Entropy Inc.: Rogers, Joel, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Endowment Management Research Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - English Department, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - F - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Faculty Club, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Faculty Members, Minority, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Fanton, Jonathan - Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - FBI, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Fellowships, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Film Associates, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Filming at Yale, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Film Curriculum, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Financial Situation, Yale, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Fitt, Alfred B., 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Five-Year B.A. Program, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Football, Centennial Celebration, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Football Highlights Film, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - Forestry School, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Forum, 1971 February 4 (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - French Department, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - Freshmen Counsellors, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - G - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Gay Alliance, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - General Bulletin, Yale University, 1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - German Consulate, Boston, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - German Library, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Gibbs Society, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Gifts and Grants, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Gifts in Kind, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Glee Club, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 188)
    - Governance, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, Association of, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 190)
    - Graduate Club Association, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - Graduate School Degrees, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 192)
    - Grants and Contracts, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 193)
    - Grant and Gift Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 194)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - Graduate School, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - Griswold (A. Whitney) Award, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Guest Accommodations, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - Guest House, University, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - Guides, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - Guiding Policy and Procedure, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 203)
    - H - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 204)
    - Hale, Nathan, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Harrison (Ross Granville) Professorship, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Harvard University, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Havemeyer House, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Health Services Center, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - I, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 210)
    - Helen Hadley Hall, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 211)
    - Henry Fellowships, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 213)
    - Higgins Survey, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - Calvin Hill Day Care Center, Inc.: by-laws, directors report, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - Calvin Hill Day Care Center, Inc., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - Calvin Hill Day Care Center, Inc., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - Calvin Hill Day Care Center, Inc., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - Historic Commission, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 219)
    - Historical Landmarks and Society, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 220)
    - Rodgkinson (Harold) Chair, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 221)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 223)
    - Hoosac School, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 224)
    - Hotels and Motels, 1963-1972, undated (Box 11, Folder 225)
    - Housing, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - I - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - IBM Briefing Session, 1972 April 27 (Box 11, Folder 228)
    - Informal Education, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 229)
    - Information Office, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 230)
    - Ingalls Rink, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 231)
    - Institute for Educational Management, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 232)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 1969-1971, undated (Box 11, Folder 233)
    - International Association of Universities, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 234)
    - International Office, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 235)
    - International Student Center, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 236)
    - Investment Policy, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 237)
    - Italian Consul General, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 238)
    - Invitations, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 239)
    - Invitations, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 240)
    - Invitations, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 241)
    - J - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 242)
    - Jarvis Collection, 100th Anniversary, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 243)
    - Jury Duty, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 246)
    - K - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 247)
    - Kent School, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 250)
    - Law School, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 252)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - Lectures - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - University Lectureship Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Library, Sterling Memorial, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Lists, Professorships named, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - Lux et Veritas. A Report on Yale Admissions 1950-1972 (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Lux et Veritas, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Lux et Veritas, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 267)
    - Mac/Mc - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 268)
    - M - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - Management Operations, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 270)
    - Master of Arts in Teaching, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 272)
    - Mathematics Building, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 273)
    - Mathematics Department Conference, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 274)
    - May Day, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 276)
    - Mecha Lecture Series, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 277)
    - Medal - Kirkwood, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 278)
    - Yale Medal, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 279)
    - Yale Medal Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 280)
    - Medical Emergency Program, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 281)
    - Medical School, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 282)
    - Mellon Fellowship, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 283)
    - Memorial Services, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 284)
    - Miller, Spencer F., Associate Treasurer, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 287)
    - M.I.T. Alumni Study, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 290)
    - Moorhead, J. Upshur - Prentice Cup Tennis Team, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 291)
    - Mory's, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 293)
    - Music School, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - N - General Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 295)
    - National Association of Independent Schools, Reassessing the Relationships between Colleges and Secondary Schools, Danforth Foundation and Institute for Development of Educational Activities, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 296)
    - National Association of Independent Schools, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 297)
    - Newcomers Club, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 298)
    - New Haven Preservation Trust, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 299)
    - New Haven Yale Club, Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 300)
    - New Journal, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 301)
    - News Bureau, University, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 302)
    - Nursing School, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 304)
    - O - General Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 305)
    - Officers, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 306)
    - Officers' Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 307)
    - Ombudsman T. Cole, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 308)
    - Old Campus - Hixon Terrace, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 309)
    - OSHA (Occupational Safety and Health Act), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 310)
    - P - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 311)
    - Parents' Day, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 312)
    - Parking Authority, Edward L. Barnes: Yale University Parking Report for Temple-Whitney Block, 1967 September 14 (Box 15, Folder 313)
    - Parking Authority, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 314)
    - Peabody Museum, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 315)
    - Personnel Office, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - Physics Department, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 317)
    - Pierson College, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 318)
    - Political Science Department, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 319)
    - Political Union, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 320)
    - Poynter Fellow, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 321)
    - Presidency Survey Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - President's Office, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 323)
    - President's Committee on Alumni Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 324)
    - President's Travel Account, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 325)
    - Press Board of Governors, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 326)
    - Yale Press Board of Governors, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 327)
      - Financial Statements, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 328)
      - Financial Forecasts, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 329)
    - Yale Press Board of Governors, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 330)
    - Yale University Press, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 331)
    - Princeton University, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 332)
    - Printing Service University, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 333)
    - Prizes, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 334)
    - Puerto Ricans' Despierta Boricua, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 335)
    - R - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 336)
    - Records, Student, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 337)
    - Research, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 339)
    - Retarded, Schools for the, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 340)
    - Reunion, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 341)
    - ROTC (Army and Navy), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 342)
    - S - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 344)
    - Yale Sailing Associates, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 345)
    - Salaries, Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 346)
    - Salaries, Faculty Comments, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 347)
    - St. Elmo Committee on Foreign Students, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 348)
    - St. John's School Building, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 349)
    - St. Marks School, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 350)
    - Scholarships, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 351)
    - Scranton Report, 1970, Fall (Box 17, Folder 352)
    - Duties - R. H. Holden Folder, 1964-1970, undated (Box 17, Folder 353)
    - Secretary's Office, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 354)
    - Secretary's Office Clock, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 355)
    - Secretary's Office Staff, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 356)
    - Selective Service and Veterans Affairs, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 357)
    - Senior Class Council, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 358)
    - Senior Seminar - Foreign Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 359)
    - University Series Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 360)
    - Sex and the [Yale] Student, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 361)
    - Sheffield Scientific School: Report upon Financial Statements, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 362)